Martin Anastasov

New York, New York, United States



martin.anastasov@yahoo.com



linkedin.com/in/martinanastasov

Summary

My professional journey has been fueled by working in extremely competitive and fast paced environments with innovative companies solving big problems through technology.

I currently support our potential partners as they navigate our organization and partner communities to ensure they are talking to the right people at the right time to resolve their most pressing opportunities.

Future computer engineer striving to make a difference in this world, one motherboard at a time.

Experience



Partner Relationship Manager

GetSwitch

Dec 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

Switch (formerly known as The Carmersson Group) is a sales consulting and investment firm bridging the gap between marketing and sales through data, automation and unique engagement strategies.

Switch works with early and growth stage companies looking to find clear product market fit, repeatable sales processes, pricing models and predictable sales forecasting for B2B and B2C companies.

In our work with companies raising up to \$50mm we have a clear formula to scale through rapid experimentation, dedicated SDRs and AEs and the development of a clear sales playbook and funnels.

Kotlin Multiplatform Relationship Manager

Touchlab

Jan 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

For almost a decade, Touchlab has been on the leading edge of mobile product development. Today that means helping our clients build products in a world where mobile platforms have matured.

When engineering leaders need to accelerate feature development, maximize engineering efficiency and future-proof their teams and products, they partner with us.

Touchlab's partnered with dozens of mobile engineering and product teams from the Fortune 100, Unicorns, and High-growth startups.

We work alongside our great partners to build unique solutions like guidance systems for forest rangers in Africa & Asia, an order-ahead app for North American coffee & donut enthusiasts, and open source mobile tools to change the way medical research gets done.

I currently support our team in working with enterprise companies exploring and piloting Kotlin Multiplatform.

Education

Semos Education

Web Page, Digital/Multimedia and Information Resources Design 2020 - 2021

- Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Information Technologies Skopje
 Bachelor of Technology BTech, Computer Engineering
 2017 2021
- Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering 2017 2021

Licenses & Certifications

- Adobe Certified Associate in Visual Design Using Adobe Photoshop Adobe Issued Dec 2020 Expires Dec 2023

 JdGG-4wkk
- Adobe Certified Associate in Graphic Design & Illustration Using Adobe
 Illustrator Adobe
 Issued Jan 2021 Expires Jan 2024
 wM5eV-H9yD
- Adobe Certified Professional in Visual Design Adobe Issued Jan 2021 Expires Dec 2023

Skills

Sales • Adobe Photoshop • JavaScript • Programming • After Effects • Unity 3D • C++ • C (Programming Language) • HTML5 • CSS